Markham Starr collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2. 2015 accrual: Against the Tide, Down On The Farm, In History's Wake, and Voices From The Waterfront photographs, March 26, 2005 through December 4, 2013, afc2013031_dc002; 841 TIFF, 4 pdf, 4 xls, and 1 m2t
  - Subseries 1. Against the Tide: The Commercial Fishermen of Point Judith RI files, March 26, 2005 through December 2, 2013, 411 TIFF, 1 pdf, 1 xls
    - A load of striped bass on deck, July 6, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Peter Nicholson welds a repair to the scallop dredge aboard the Njord, March 1, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Peter Nicholson welds a repair to the scallop dredge aboard the Njord. Fishermen must be able to fix nearly everything aboard the vessel while at sea or lose the trip.
    - Boats hauled on a railway opposite Point Jude for painting and repair, August 22, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Boats hauled on a railway opposite Point Jude for painting and repair. The wooden boat in the foreground never went back into the water. This facility closed shortly after because new environmental regulations made the operation too costly to continue. The shipyard was turned into a yachting center, the fate of most waterfront properties once dedicated to fishermen.
    - Summer Girl, July 28, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Summer Girl. Many fishermen, once they get past the age of wanting to go to sea on bigger boats, invest in skiffs or other small boats such as this and dayfish at the end of their careers. With low overhead and less responsibility, they can keep fishing and maintain some income.
    - View of a stern ramp on a trawler, February 22, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      View of a stern ramp on a trawler. The western rig revolutionized the industry. With a net reel aft, the complicated process of setting out or retrieving the net as was done on eastern rigs was reduced to pushing buttons. This, along with improvements in electronic navigation, allowed nearly anyone with the money to get into fishing, leading to the current problems of having overfished New England's waters.
    - Charles McGowan unloads totes of crabs from the Stormy Elizabeth during a blizzard at Point Judith, March 16, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Jeffrey Jordan and Adam Dyer bailing crabs from the wetwell aboard Entrapment. Jeffrey Jordan (left) Adam Dyer (right), December 13, 2006, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Heritage returning home from a trip to Georges Bank, February 23, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Bernard O'Hagen returns from a day lobstering on the Martha Porter, February 18, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Bernard O'Hagen returns from a day lobstering on the Martha Porter. Note his frozen beard. The Martha Porter also gillnets at other times of the year.
    - A metal worker burns off a piece of steel aloft as he makes repairs to a vessel's rigging, February 8, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Looking aft from the pilot house of the Kelsi & Morgan to the back deck where Charlie Brayton and Douglas Stone sort fish, July 11, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Looking aft from the pilot house of the Kelsi & Morgan to the back deck where Charlie Brayton and Douglas Stone sort fish. The vessel is named after two of Charlie's grandchildren, seen in the photos at the top of the image. Charlie Brayton (left) Douglas Stone (right)
    - Two fishermen hardening the trap at Black Rock from a skiff. Jesus Nieves (left) Saul Umana (right), May 31, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Elizabeth Helen trawling inside Block Island Sound with a schooner sailing in the background, June 11, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Elizabeth Helen trawling inside Block Island Sound with a schooner sailing in the background. This vessel was lost a few years later when she flipped at sea after a load shifted. Both people survived the accident.
    - Two trawlers pass each other on Georges Bank on a calm day as pilot whales take advantage of whatever fish are stirred up, February 28, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Two trawlers pass each other on Georges Bank on a calm day as pilot whales take advantage of whatever fish are stirred up. The whales know to follow trawlers for easy meals.
    - The Barbara Ann heads to sea on an offshore lobster trip in the fog, May 10, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      The Barbara Ann heads to sea on an offshore lobster trip in the fog. Tragically, a crewman was caught in a set of gear going overboard and was killed on this voyage.
    - The Linda Marie dives into the trough between waves while trawling off Block Island for groundfish, March 15, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - The Deborah Lee returns to her dock, April 2, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Hand painted scene on the back of a fish truck at Point Judith, May 25, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Pilot whales feeding behind a trawler on Georges Bank, March 1, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Pilot whales feeding behind a trawler on Georges Bank. These whales know when a vessel hauls back that dinner is served. They will appear from nowhere and eat the fish discarded from the haulback, disappearing again once the feast is over.
    - The old ice house at Point Judith, January 6, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      The old ice house at Point Judith. A newer facility still operates north of this building to provide trawlers with ice for their trips. Once shoreside facilities disappear, they never return. This has happened to nearly every port in New England - waterfront property turns into condos and stores, lost forever to fishermen.
    - Auto pilot, bible, and other gear in the pilothouse of the Captain Robert, owned by Mike Marchetti, March 14, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Auto pilot, bible, and other gear in the pilothouse of the Captain Robert, owned by Mike Marchetti. Mike is not particularly religious, but perhaps believes it couldn't hurt...
    - Raymond Livernois, owner of the Vic Ter Rae, at the helm on Georges Bank, March 2, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Raymond Livernois, owner of the Vic Ter Rae, at the helm on Georges Bank. Ray was thrown out of his house as a teenager and started working on the docks, eventually working his way up to owner and captain of one of the biggest vessels in the port. This story was typical for most owners - most started as deckhands and worked their way to the top, something that is no longer possible for young men and women entering the industry as there are no licenses available anymore.
    - Crew hardening the trap net at Black Rock. Roland "Bucky" Smith, James Main, Brad Stanton (left to right), May 10, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Lobster trap turning block, made in Tenant's Harbor Maine, May 2, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Lobster trap turning block, made in Tenant's Harbor Maine. The warp for the lobster traps passes through this block on its way to the pot hauler.
    - William Cote of the Emme Jade tosses out old bait from a lobster trap just hauled inside the Harbor of Refuge, August 20, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Gloves drying on a line inside The Bait Company building, May 25, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Gloves drying on a line inside The Bait Company building. Owned by Andrea Incollingo, the operation supplies bait to lobstermen year round.
  - Subseries 2. Down On The Farm: The Last Dairy Farms of North Stonington files, October 2, 2007 through November 2010, 260 TIFF, 1 pdf, 1 xls
    Files, primarily photographs, created during Starr's project. Also included is one inventory spreadsheet containing descriptive data for every photo and a digital copy of Starr's book Down On The Farm: The Last Dairy Farms of North Stonington.
    The digital files on disk have not been rearranged from their original order. The manuscript files have been described in alphabetical order in the finding aid and the photographs are listed in numerical order by ID number. The photographs' titles and ID numbers are copied from Starr's item level metadata in his descriptive spreadsheet "Down on the Farm The Last Dairy Farms of North Stonington.xls". The descriptions and listings of individuals in the photos are used as titles. If a description was too long to be an effective title archivists shortened it and recorded the original description in the item's Scope and Content note. The dates come from the files' EXIF metadata except where those dates are clearly inaccurate. Archivists estimated accurate dates when necessary. See the inventory and files' metadata for more context.
    - Down On The Farm: The Last Dairy Farms of North Stonington, November 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 pdf
    - Photo inventory, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 xls
    - View of George & Carrol Miner Farm field, November 26, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - View of Cool Breeze Farm corn field and barn, May 28, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Valley View Farm barns and milking rooms, Sep 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - 2000lb bag of winter wheat spread for cover crop at Valley View Farm, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Cows heading in to be milked at Valley View Farm, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Cows heading in to be milked at Valley View Farm - note: no formal milking parlor on this farm
    - Ben Learned spreading winter wheat cover crop on Valley View Farm, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Tim Learned milking cows at Valley View Farm, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Tim Learned removing old silage at Valley View Farm, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Calf at Beriah Lewis Farm, January 10, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Grain silos at Beriah Lewis Farm, November 26, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Entrance to Geo & Carrol Miner Farm milking parlor with kid's drawing "Make a cow happy - Drink Milk," December 7, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Winter at Cool Breeze farm - upper fields, January 14, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - View from behind farmhouse of barns at Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, December 7, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Milking parlor at Palmer Farm showing cow hip rests, January 10, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Winter at Cool Breeze farm - sheds opposite farmhouse, January 14, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Unused grain silo and tractor with silage wagon at Palmer Farm, November 29, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Barn complex at Geo & Carrol Miner farm - milk room on left, December 28, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Cow at watercooler at Cool Breeze Farm - automatic water fill, January 2, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Curious cow at Cool Breeze Farm, January 2, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Old milk storage house on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, December 7, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Old milk storage house on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm. Cold spring water was used to cool milk before days of refrigeration.
    - Cast iron tubs used as water troughs in field - Cool Breeze Farm, January 18, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Old iron - dead tractor at Palmer Farm, November 29, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Grain and scoop at Palmer Farm, December 5, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Old corn cribs on Palmer farm, once also used to house pigs, November 29, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Manure spreader for solids at Beriah Lewis Farm, December 3, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Manure spreader for solids at Beriah Lewis Farm - most manure on farm is liquefied and sprayed but some is still spread this way.
    - Beriah Lewis Farm ventilator on main barn, December 3, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Beriah Lewis Farm storage shed with corn silage pile in background, December 3, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Bell hanging in barn on Palmer Farm, December 5, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Cow in winter eating hay on Palmer Farm, December 5, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Will Learned in milk tank room - cleaning equipment - Valley View Farm, September 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Tim Learned bringing fresh corn silage to cows using skid-steer loader, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - John Palmer and wife Patricia on farmhouse porch, October 6, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      John Palmer and wife Patricia on farmhouse porch - John works the Palmer farm with brother George, Patricia works with her step father Nyles and her mother Esther and sister Linda on Cool Breeze Farm.
    - Tractor and solid manure spreader at Valley View Farm, September 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Esther and daughter Linda Miner milking goats on Cool Breeze Farm, September 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Esther and daughter Linda Miner milking goats on Cool Breeze Farm. They do not sell goat milk but use it themselves to make cheese. They also sell goats as a sideline to milk production. Esther Miner left, Linda Miner right.
    - George Palmer on tractor planting corn - Palmer farm, May 16, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Small tractor with water tank for cows in front of unused grain silo on Cool Breeze Farm, January 2, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - George Palmer on tractor planting corn, May 16, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      George Palmer on tractor planting corn. Stopped to check seed level in hoppers - Palmer farm.
    - Double eleven milking parlor at Beriah Lewis Farm, December 28, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Double eleven milking parlor at Beriah Lewis Farm. Ledyard Lewis center facing camera, Ted Lewis right - left man unidentified.
    - Otter in pond on Cool Breeze Farm, January 14, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Otter in pond on Cool Breeze Farm - pond built by Nyles Miner.
    - Beriah Lewis Farm tractors working big field, May 11, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Beriah Lewis Farm tractors working big field - tractor on left harrowing field ahead of tractor planting corn on right.
    - Nyles Miner scraping manure from barnyard in skid-steer loader, January 2, 2008, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Nyles Miner scraping manure from barnyard in skid-steer loader - note half tire bolted to bucket used to scrape surface. Cool Breeze Farm.
    - Nyles Miner square bailing hay on Cool Breeze Farm in background, August 8, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Nyles Miner square bailing hay on Cool Breeze Farm in background. Hay rake in foreground.
    - Calf number 10 in individual pen at Beriah Lewis Farm, March 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Linda Miner spreading straw bedding in open calf shed on Cool Breeze Farm in winter, March 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Linda Miner spreading straw bedding in open calf shed on Cool Breeze Farm in winter. Linda Miner
    - George Palmer planting corn on Palmer Farm, May 16, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - John Palmer spreading solid manure on field belonging to Palmer farm, September 22, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      John Palmer spreading solid manure on field belonging to Palmer farm. Palmer farm mostly sprays liquid manure.
    - Patricia Miner adds anti-fungal liquid to chopper, May 31, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Patricia Miner adds anti-fungal liquid to chopper - this is sprayed on haylage to keep it from molding.
    - Liquid manure sprayed on corn field at Beriah Lewis Farm, April 20, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Liquid manure sprayed on corn field at Beriah Lewis Farm
    - Carrol Miner, May 26, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Unidentified worker driving portable feeder back to Beriah Lewis Farm, April 20, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Mark Taylor on tractor feeding road calves, April 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Patricia Miner packing haylage with tractor, May 31, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Patricia Miner packing haylage with tractor - Nyles Miner in background chopping hay into haylage.
    - Robert Miner on tractor on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, May 22, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Robert Miner on tractor on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm round bailing hay into 1000lb bales, May 22, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Robert Miner on tractor on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm round bailing hay into 1000lb bales. This newer technique saves much labor and time over square baling, as square bales must be left to dry for 4-5 days and be stored by hand in barns. Round bales dry one day and are then wrapped in airtight plastic to ferment. They are also stored outside and moved by tractor.
    - Shadow cast by unused silo at Palmer Farm onto roof of old stanchion barn, September 20, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Shadow cast by unused silo at Palmer Farm onto roof of old stanchion barn. Cows on all farms in town are now housed in freestall barns, not stanchion barns, but these older barns are still used for other purposes.
    - Carrol Miner square bailing dry hay on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, August 14, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Foggy day on Cool Breeze Farm. Tubs used to water cows, October 5, 2007, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Foggy day on Cool Breeze Farm. Tubs used to water cows. Cemetery in background has a tombstone marking the burial of a favorite horse from the 1800's.
    - Gene Anderson tedding hay on Beriah Lewis Farm, May 31, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Tractor and barn on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, May 26, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Robert Miner chopping hay into silage in upper field behind farmhouse on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, September 16, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Orrin Miner, September 16, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Orrin Miner - son of Carrol and Betty Miner - Their only child that works on the farm Orrin Miner
    - Patricia Miner adjusts round bailer on Cool Breeze Farm, June 22, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Bailing straw for bedding for Palmer Farm. Becky Loignon (on tractor) and Chris Buck, June 17, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Robert Miner chopping corn in upper field on Geo & Carrol Minor Farm, September 9, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Robert Miner chopping corn in upper field on Geo & Carrol Minor Farm. Robert is the son on George Minor (deceased at time of photos) and nephew of Carrol Miner.
    - Two oxen at Beriah Lewis Farm, August 5, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Two oxen at Beriah Lewis Farm. Ted Lewis keeps oxen as a hobby - up to a dozen teams - for ox-pulls at country fairs and is known throughout New England for his skill with these animals.
    - Round baled hay for haylage, June 29, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Round baled hay for haylage - stored in airtight plastic to allow it to ferment. 1000lb bales.
    - Carrol Miner and nephew Robert Miner square baling hay on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, August 14, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Carrol Miner and nephew Robert Miner square baling hay on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm. Carrol Miner on tractor, Robert on hay-wagon.
    - Corn coming up on Cool Breeze Farm, July 23, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Beriah Lewis Farm, March 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Breeding chart for herd, March 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Breeding chart for herd. Tracks each animal's progress from breeding to birth of calf. Beriah Lewis Farm.
    - Double-four DeLaval milking parlor on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, June 14, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Nyles Miner chopping hay on Cool Breeze Farm, May 31, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Geo & Carrol Miner Farm barns with hay rake in field, August 11, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Chopping corn silage on Beriah Lewis Farm, September 9, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Chopping corn silage on Beriah Lewis Farm - given the hundreds and hundreds of acres of corn planted, this farm hires a 6 row chopper to quickly bring in the crop. Trucks from the farm carry the silage to the horizontal pits in a continuous stream.
    - A full truck of chopped corn heads back to the pits at Beriah Lewis Farm, September 9, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Cows walk back to the freestall barn after milking on Beriah Lewis Farm, August 5, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Cows walk back to the freestall barn after milking on Beriah Lewis Farm. This farm, unlike the other four, milks three times a day rather than twice.
    - 1993 Federated Genetics poster hanging in barn on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, August 27, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      1993 Federated Genetics poster hanging in barn on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm. While most of the farms still keep a bull, most of the breeding is done artificially, and this chart showed what animals were available and their qualities.
    - Picking up round baled hay with a bale hugger. Carrol Miner on left, Robert Miner on right, May 26, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Trimming hooves of cow that is out for surgery, June 29, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Trimming hooves of cow that is out for surgery. This cow had a twisted stomach which a vet is operating on off camera. Robert takes advantage of the situation to trim the hooves while the cow is knocked out.
    - John Clegg on tractor, June 10, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      John Clegg on tractor. John is in charge of planting and harvesting, as well as for feeding most of the animals on the farm (nearly a thousand animals).
    - Carrol Miner and Boots, his dog, May 26, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Carrol Miner and Boots, his dog. Boots is always with Carrol, sometimes even on the tractor.
    - Carrol and Orrin Miner moving a large bag of seed, May 26, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Carrol and Orrin Miner moving a large bag of seed. Carrol Miner on left, Orrin Miner on right.
    - John Clegg on tractor dumping corn silage into the mixing wagon as he mixes feed for the herd, August 5, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      John Clegg on tractor dumping corn silage into the mixing wagon as he mixes feed for the herd. Feed consists of a mixture of corn silage, grasses, brewers grains, and molasses.
    - Spraying liquid manure onto hay field. Neil Main in tractor, May 11, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Mark Taylor on tractor leaves the field where he has just fed the road calves, April 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Mark Taylor on tractor leaves the field where he has just fed the road calves - calves that are down the road from the farm itself.
    - Linda Miner milking a goat, September 16, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Linda Miner milking a goat. Her goats provide additional income on the farm when babies are sold to others.
    - Milking parlor at Cool Breeze Farm, August 27, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Noah Lewis, one of the 8th generation on the farm, in the milking parlor on Beriah Lewis Farm, May 27, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Palmer Farm in the Clarks Falls section of town, June 14, 2010, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Every Day Quality Feed bag, August 27, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Every Day Quality Feed bag. Now plastic, these bags are used only once. When they were made of cotton, feed bags were often made into household goods such as pillow cases, curtains, or clothes by Betty Miner.
    - Robert Miner welding a new tailgate for their dump truck, August 27, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
      Robert Miner welding a new tailgate for their dump truck. Farmers must be able to fix most equipment on their own to stay afloat financially.
    - Grain silos on Beriah Lewis Farm, August 28, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF
    - Repairing a flat tire on a tractor on Geo & Carrol Miner Farm, August 27, 2009, afc2013031_dc002; 1 TIFF